[
   {
        "question": "After 5 years of service, Susan Mathews finally asked her boss to give _______ a pay.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "she"
                },
                {
                    "text": "her"

                },
                {
                    "text": "hers"
                },
                {
                    "text": "herself"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "011001032332010003211"
    },
	{
        "question": "Ms.Jennifer Hong has beeen a _____ colleague of mine for seven years and it has been pleasure to work with her.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "close"
                },
                {
                    "text": "closely"

                },
                {
                    "text": "closing"
                },
                {
                    "text": "closure"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "201200111220010012303"
    },
	{
        "question": "A banquet is beeing held in honor of the governor _____ political career began in 1989 in an uderground student movement and spanned almost quarter a century.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "who"
                },
                {
                    "text": "whom"

                },
                {
                    "text": "which"
                },
                {
                    "text": "whose"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "213231020210232013313"
    },
	{
        "question": "The school announced that all handout materials will be supplied in class ____ now on.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "until"
                },
                {
                    "text": "and"

                },
                {
                    "text": "since"
                },
                {
                    "text": "from"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "203322312312203100012"
    },
	{
        "question": "_____ boarding the aircraft, passengers with small children and passengers with disabilities will be given priority.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "During"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Due to"

                },
                {
                    "text": "When"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Because"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "023300112123012021121"
    },
	{
        "question": "The information provided may be inaccurate or outdated; users of the information use it at their own ____.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "risk"
                },
                {
                    "text": "cost"

                },
                {
                    "text": "danger"
                },
                {
                    "text": "hazard"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "123212023320011102000"
    },
	{
        "question": "Conventional wisdom has it that ____ more and more women become a part of the nation's managerial and excutive work force , they encounted conflict between work and non=work roles.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "as"
                },
                {
                    "text": "both"

                },
                {
                    "text": "until"
                },
                {
                    "text": "whether"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "002023013102201332321"
    },
	{
        "question": "I am writing ____ behalf of Mr.William to inform you of the alteration in the date of our upcoming meeting in Tokyo.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "at"
                },
                {
                    "text": "on"

                },
                {
                    "text": "for"
                },
                {
                    "text": "to"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "131321030213330213322"
    },
	{
        "question": "When Sunlop Corporation moved its headquarters to Chicago, the director had a state-of-the-art security system ____.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "installing"
                },
                {
                    "text": "install"

                },
                {
                    "text": "installed"
                },
                {
                    "text": "installs"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "321103101031200023303"
    },
	{
        "question": "On May 6, Mr.Smith will discuss ____ approaches for the advancement of our new goods.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "addition"
                },
                {
                    "text": "additional"

                },
                {
                    "text": "additionally"
                },
                {
                    "text": "additions"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "013121013310003231123"
    },
	{
        "question": "Moving away from the city and renting an apartment in the rural area does not always help ____ one's living expenses.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "limit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "limited"

                },
                {
                    "text": "limiting"
                },
                {
                    "text": "limitation"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "002100010312323100033"
    },
	{
        "question": "The Progress Group facilitated the design of a set of incremental steps to ____ its objectives.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "accelerate"
                },
                {
                    "text": "accumulate"

                },
                {
                    "text": "accentuate"
                },
                {
                    "text": "accomplish"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "102232110013222323001"
    },
	{
        "question": "The market research report was full of ____ prediction about exchange rates that later proved completely wrong.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "compel"
                },
                {
                    "text": "compelled"

                },
                {
                    "text": "the compelled"
                },
                {
                    "text": "compelling"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "323111030003323031012"
    },
	{
        "question": "Ms.Yoon was involved in the preparation of a common set of principles for _____ productivity.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "achieve"
                },
                {
                    "text": "achiever"

                },
                {
                    "text": "achieving"
                },
                {
                    "text": "achievement"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "103110030111022221211"
    },
	{
        "question": "A career choice is ____ one has to decide for oneself.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "everything"
                },
                {
                    "text": "nothing"

                },
                {
                    "text": "something"
                },
                {
                    "text": "anything"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "230320213133012112201"
    },
	{
        "question": "You shall be ____ no obligation to accept any offer and may, at your discretion, discontinue membership after two years.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "under"
                },
                {
                    "text": "making"

                },
                {
                    "text": "able to"
                },
                {
                    "text": "used to"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "001110001031213032200"
    },
	{
        "question": "All cellular phones should be turned off while the concert is in _____.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "playing"
                },
                {
                    "text": "performance"

                },
                {
                    "text": "progress"
                },
                {
                    "text": "practice"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "032221010302232211212"
    },
	{
        "question": "Currently, BDH Corp. is looking at making additional changes in the management strategies that will continue to ____ its employees.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "benefit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "benefiting"

                },
                {
                    "text": "beneficial"
                },
                {
                    "text": "beneficiary"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "311033030020133300332"
    },
	{
        "question": "I feel sorry to inform you that I am unable to ____ your request to join the Mid-Europe Convention.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "admit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "assert"

                },
                {
                    "text": "accept"
                },
                {
                    "text": "appear"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "312331120331321013323"
    },
	{
        "question": "Under the revised procedure, efforts have been _____ by the government to ensure that the emerging exporters have adequate access to the credit facilities.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "taken"
                },
                {
                    "text": "made"

                },
                {
                    "text": "done"
                },
                {
                    "text": "started"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "022013000123330101130"
    },
	{
        "question": "The reason for this failure ____ is directly related to the fact that workers do not read the instruction manual before operating equipment.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "occur"
                },
                {
                    "text": "occuring"

                },
                {
                    "text": "occurred"
                },
                {
                    "text": "occures"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "132132232023033103303"
    },
	{
        "question": "The organization works to engage individuals to take greater responsibility for keeping their communities ____.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "beauty"
                },
                {
                    "text": "beautifier"

                },
                {
                    "text": "beautiful"
                },
                {
                    "text": "beautifully"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "302323133102133311030"
    },
	{
        "question": "Prize winners who do not pick up their VCRs at the _____ stores within three months negate their rights to the prizes.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "designated"
                },
                {
                    "text": "assigned"

                },
                {
                    "text": "reserved"
                },
                {
                    "text": "dedicated"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "133310201220320021031"
    },
	{
        "question": "A good manager ____ an environment where ideas are heard and respected and everyone feels that they are contributing to the whole.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "create"
                },
                {
                    "text": "creates"

                },
                {
                    "text": "is created"
                },
                {
                    "text": "creating"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "332122333110203320223"
    },
	{
        "question": "At the end of the test, students are asked to ____ their tests face down on the desk near the exit.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "write"
                },
                {
                    "text": "prepare"

                },
                {
                    "text": "collect"
                },
                {
                    "text": "place"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "012110202022021330333"
    },
	{
        "question": "A plethora of study programs now available online has made it possible for working people to gain certificates or degrees far ____ than ever before.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "more easily"
                },
                {
                    "text": "easier"

                },
                {
                    "text": "easiest"
                },
                {
                    "text": "easily"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "301313300230302022100"
    },
	{
        "question": "Hundreds of outlets _____ in the market fire started by an overturned gas range, despite fire-fighters's effort to put out the flames.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "perished"
                },
                {
                    "text": "disappeared"

                },
                {
                    "text": "ruined"
                },
                {
                    "text": "excited"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "003013310111000313201"
    },
	{
        "question": "Under the new regulations, spending on office equipment and photocopier _____ will be strictly controlled.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "used"
                },
                {
                    "text": "using"

                },
                {
                    "text": "user"
                },
                {
                    "text": "usage"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "200333300300121003012"
    },
	{
        "question": "Employees wanting to attend the Christmas Ball can ____ tickets to the event at the front desk in the Personnel Department.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "join in"
                },
                {
                    "text": "pick up"

                },
                {
                    "text": "get over"
                },
                {
                    "text": "find out"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "032112010212013220310"
    },
	{
        "question": "Graduates holding an MBA degree are _____ competitive these days due to growing skepticism about the value of the education.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "less"
                },
                {
                    "text": "more"

                },
                {
                    "text": "better"
                },
                {
                    "text": "fewer"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "100002021210033301013"
    },
	{
        "question": "The resistance _____ by the firm's staff made it very difficult to conduct the audit efficiently.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "built"
                },
                {
                    "text": "taken"

                },
                {
                    "text": "furnished"
                },
                {
                    "text": "encountered"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "030230312103202013300"
    },
	{
        "question": "The County Commision is still waiting for word from the Kansas City Railroard Company concerning repairs _____ to be done at threes crossings.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "need"
                },
                {
                    "text": "needs"

                },
                {
                    "text": "needed"
                },
                {
                    "text": "necessary"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "122100003331333003132"
    },
	{
        "question": "The processors they are now promoting are ____ designed for cell phones and wireless PDAs.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "specifically"
                },
                {
                    "text": "eagerly"

                },
                {
                    "text": "optionally"
                },
                {
                    "text": "eventually"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "120030302101333001010"
    },
	{
        "question": "Ever since he ____ , he has endeavored to push certain policies through that are quite unpopular with the general public.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "had elected"
                },
                {
                    "text": "is elected"

                },
                {
                    "text": "was elected"
                },
                {
                    "text": "will elect"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "120321301203333131013"
    },
	{
        "question": "The newest Chrysler sedan is both stylishly modeled and _____ at a reasonable price, providing consumers with an attractive car for people of all age groups.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "offers"
                },
                {
                    "text": "offering"

                },
                {
                    "text": "offered"
                },
                {
                    "text": "offer"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "013121331011201012021"
    },
	{
        "question": "To remain _____ for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a degree according to the guidelines.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "eligible"
                },
                {
                    "text": "entitled"

                },
                {
                    "text": "responsible"
                },
                {
                    "text": "considerate"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "232001313011202213101"
    },
	{
        "question": "The managers hope that the new plan will increase sales both in the coming year and ____",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "beyond"
                },
                {
                    "text": "within"

                },
                {
                    "text": "above"
                },
                {
                    "text": "along"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "121221030223320030112"
    },
	{
        "question": "The original _____ of the city's significant museum will be preserved during the restitution proces.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "curriculum"
                },
                {
                    "text": "symptom"

                },
                {
                    "text": "appearance"
                },
                {
                    "text": "behavior"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "233011013013310012101"
    },
	{
        "question": "In order to provide a better service to _____, Smallville's traveller information desk has been expanded.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "visit"
                },
                {
                    "text": "visitors"

                },
                {
                    "text": "visiting"
                },
                {
                    "text": "visitation"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "101311111332101120120"
    },
	{
        "question": "Her comments made on her dining experience suggested that she was more than _____ with the food and service.",
        "type": "grammar",
        "content":{
            "multichoices": [
                {
                    "text": "satisfying"
                },
                {
                    "text": "satisfactory"

                },
                {
                    "text": "satisfied"
                },
                {
                    "text": "satisfaction"
                }
            ]
        },
        "answer": "021033132311310120331"
    }
]